guinotusa.com 2018-05-03

# Privacy Policy - Guinot - Professional skin care products and skin treatments

**Our Commitment:**

Guinot USA / Lachman Imports is committed to safeguarding your privacy online and protecting the information that we collect. Under no circumstances do we disclose information about you, or resell any information collected through this site. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our data-handling practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**IP address:**

****We may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address each time you visit our web site. The IP address is a unique identifier assigned to your computer each time you connect to the Internet. The IP address is used for site traffic statistical reporting and analysis, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to help protect our customers and ourselves from fraud.

**Cookies:**

****Our website uses cookies to keep temporarily stored information during a multi-page process, such as when placing an order. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive. You have the choice to accept all cookies, or to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies, by setting the appropriate options in your browser. We only use cookies when there is persistent data that is required to be kept from one page to another, such as when completing an order. If you decide not to accept a cookie, you may not be able to proceed with an order.

**Server Activity:**

****Customer logins, and other server access activities, are monitored and analyzed to protect our server from unauthorized login attempts.

**Correspondence:**

We reserve the right to keep a record of any correspondence (i.e. email or paper mail) submitted by you to us.

**Disclosure of Information:**

****We cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this privacy policy. For example, we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government, law enforcement or legal counsel (e.g. by court order).

**Security Measures:**

****No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make the best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**General:**

****This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of this site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites.

If you have any questions with regards to this statement please send them to:

Lachman Imports

230 Fifth Avenue

Suite 900

New York, NY 10001
